<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<reviews>
	<review id="1">
		<review-text>I had redmi 6 Pro and exchanged it for Redmi 11.
But I'm not impressed with the phone.
Display looks normal and I don't think its better than Redmi 6 pro. I still feel Redmi 6 pro screen is best.
Camera is really a avg one. Not worth it.
Prev Redmi phones were really good, camera quality too will be good
This one doesn't fit in to Redmi family. Though it has good specifications, it doesn't worth.
Fast charger is good, charges really fast.
If you just need a phone you can go for this phone... more review after a week.

Review after couple of weeks - March 8 2022.
Display - Doesnt look like AMOLED display. For me its like a ordinary one.
Battery: It charges really fast and it can withstand for a day.
Use: I nvr did gaming on this phone. Just using for call &amp; whatsapp. Sometime, screen flashes and some app crashes. Happens atleast once or twice a day. call quality is good. Though I've 6GB RAM, it nvr behaves it has 6GB of RAM.
This phone can be used for ppl, who need a phone wiht big display and battery.
camera is really bad. Don't know why Redmi is doing like this. Pictures looks normal outside with good sunlight. Under tubelight, could see more noises in picture. Not at all happy with camera.
Read more</review-text>
		<review-year>India</review-year>
	</review>
	<review id="2">
		<review-text>For 12500/- price it's a good pic

Screen Amoled - 5/5
Sounds -5/5
Look /Design -4/5
Performance -5/5
(Do not expect more than what it can in this price bro)
Battery Backup - 4.5/5
For Heavy games - 3.5/5
Cameras - 3.5/5
(Not Upto mark but try Camera360 as a primary camera will makes our phone cam 4.5/5)
IR blaster - 5/5
Finger Sensor-5/5
Face Unlock- 4/5
Fast Charging 33W (loved it)
Bluetooth v5.0 - 5/5

Cons:
Unwanted Apps Preloaded
I felt some laggy when playing heavy games
No FM
Annoying Some MI Apps and mi app store + Their Annoying Notification ( Recommend to Turn off their notification)
Read more</review-text>
		<review-year>India</review-year>
	</review>
	<review id="3">
		<review-text>Pros- Amoled Screen, Battery easily lasts a day or day n half on moderate usage.Charging Speed, Size of the mobile which is handy can b accessed though single hand..Separate SD card slot.
CONS- CAMERA low light pictures are worst...A Big Dissapoinment, Price should have been a 1000 less considering processor, No 5G..</review-text>
		<review-year>India</review-year>
	</review>
	<review id="4">
		<review-text></review-text>
		<review-year>India</review-year>
	</review>
	<review id="5">
		<review-text> Hello all,

Am new to redmi(note 11), yesterday I received new mobile and please find my observation at below.

Am not a gaming user, am moderate user(daily usage) so i preferred Snapdragon 680 chip with 6nm architecture, but in the Redmi note 11 the chip is different Snapdragon 665 with 11 nm architecture.

So please be awareness. The issue in company level not Amazon.

So Am returning the same mobile.

For your reference I have attached screen recorded, please find the same.

Note: They have mentioned in the box, mobile(about option) as snapdragon &quot;680&quot; But they used 665 chipset instead of 680.

Simply waste of money for 15k budget please go for other branding mobile.

Thanks.
Read more</review-text>
		<review-year>India</review-year>
	</review>
	<review id="6">
		<review-text>Redmi Note 11 is great piece, but automatic call recording option is not proper.
Request to Xiaomi Mi for updates that.</review-text>
		<review-year>India</review-year>
	</review>
	<review id="7">
		<review-text> A good fone in this price range display,sound, design excellent camara also good .always on display is not available always it is a gimmick after ten second display tun of automaticaly not available always why they saying always an display for this.miui 13 is nothing need more updates also 4 k recording not provided it is a major drawback for a amoled display even note seven pro my old phone have 4k 30 fos. Recording lack of 5 g is not big matter because even 4g is not providing properly by net works so forget 5g it is only for metros no laging or heating issues charging is superb by 33watt hyper charging .very good phone for normal uses I am not a Gamer so iam unable to say about gaming after 10 days use iam satisfied with this phone
Read more</review-text>
		<review-year>India</review-year>
	</review>
	<review id="8">
		<review-text>This is not an upgaradation of previous models like Note 9 &amp; Note 10.
Only display and Battery is highlight of this phone.
Camera performance was very bad and low light performance terrible.
The performance of processor is averge.
Pricing of this phone should be 10k</review-text>
		<review-year>India</review-year>
	</review>
</reviews>
